[Music]
hi everybody this is just a quick
announcement about Movember so Movember
in case anyone doesn't know is a charity
that encourages men to grow a mustache
in order to raise money for men's health
and we are gonna do it this year and
we're gonna do it with a little bit of a
twist so we're gonna be raising money to
help prevent male suicide which is
something that's very close to our
hearts a lot of the men who've been on
our rebel wisdom weekend have had
fathers brothers friends who died too
young and so we'd really like to help
Movember raise money to support that so
normally what happens is that someone
grows a mustache which in this case will
be me growing a probably quite
embarrassing mustache I'm not
particularly genetically hairy shall we
say but let's see how it goes and if we
raise over a thousand pounds David is
going to as we all know David is fully
bearded what what are you going to do
David if we raise over a thousand pounds
if we raise over a thousand pounds I'm
going to shave off my beard at the rebel
wisdom Christmas party at the end of
November so if you're in London come to
the rebel wisdom Christmas party and
we'll make some kind of event I'm
thinking about maybe kind of doing
different like moustache types may be
doing mutton chops and then shaving it
off for charity and just to let you guys
know if Ali can do it anyone can do it
so really yeah and it is really close to
our hearts we've had it's interesting of
the the the two journalists who came to
our men's weekend's
tim lot and then bradshaw from the BBC
both came because and talked about in
their articles a friend of those who
committed suicide and how they thought
that that kind of work a bit more kind
of emotional honesty a bit more
connection would have made a big
difference a bit more brotherhood would
have made a big difference to their and
their friends so that's yeah it's it's a
really good cause and it's one that's
really important to us and if you want
to get involved those basically two ways
you can either join us and grow as well
and you can kind of
have your own account on November and
then join the rebel ISM team you just
search join a team join rebel wisdom and
then the money all gets pulled together
so that's one way you can get absolutely
just join in which would be amazing or
you can just donate straight up and
we'll put all the information in the
show notes here I will be publishing
stuff on our Facebook and the community
tab throughout the month tracking my
moustache progress and then will posted
a lot of pictures of David and various
states of mutton-chop are-- and who
knows what else from the Christmas party
so hope you can support thanks a lot for
listening and we'll see you soon